hua hai
a very good morning friends welcome you to
ark they should arrive safe mission possible so
let's get varna ksana we welcome you to ark they should arrive at
this ashram eleventh day nurse anand hai
is the question audio screens
now suhag you can see in widescreen 2
question adv1 driving u c v good care
in vehicle that gotra producing outside
you will speed up aranod dahi kal no death
registration number of the beginning from
authorities alive option pass and proceed in
home only to shoulder displease where you can see
subscribe thank you we can see on
highway if you go to a little remote areas
or and we will tell you just a little bit on the
wrong side then the
ring of strength there is a lot
and it becomes very hi relationships so at that
time veer if
you face such a situation when you travel then what will you do then
please join us
and we request you  That
you are not alone, you should join your family, your
friends, your love partner
and become a part of this campaign and
become a partner in making your day just because we
face all these things on delivery wheels
and we face so many problems
because of this so many lives are lost due to small
mistakes, due to small carelessness,
so we come and connect with you
and every time we come with new questions, there are
all kinds of questions related to this, there are such
situations which
we face almost on daily basis, so what should we do in that, tell us,
you tell us, join us
and by joining this you
have a chance to win exciting prizes,
so be a part of the discussion, Prince Change
Anar Indian Roads said that which is
given in this question now that you are driving,
you saw that there is a vehicle carrying goods, there are
big lies, drops and those  There are some
big examples, that is,
things are coming out of it, so what will you do at that
time, you will increase your speed and
overtake it and get out of it
or you will note down its registration number
and inform the authorities
because that becomes very risky or you will let
that cycle go and then we will go
or you can tell it by blowing the horn very loudly that
you did not like this thing, then you can
tell us through this what is your answer
and the second skin question of the day, now
you have a lot of chances on which
today this question will be for only two hours,
you can join the eyes and
you can register your answer anytime and
after 2 hours, our classmates who will come from Hindu will
join you and will bring a new
question,
you can participate in that too with you, the
most interesting thing is that on a
daily basis you bring 5 questions every 2 hours
and we will answer all
those five one by one  You
can participate in the questions and this
is your chance to win not just
one but many exciting prizes,
you can send
in a single day, you can add
and on your side your gym is working completely, this is
related to road safety to make people aware,
now we are doing the road safety show, now in this
we want that you are not alone, these are the people you
love,
your family members,
your friends, whom you want to see safe on the
rollers, you can
join them in this and contribute in making
your day just by being a part of this campaign, in taking this campaign forward, your interest in making it just,
and our question answers on the zones
starts at night, in that App launch speaking,
we give you our results,
Om does Bigg Boss
nouns and you can go and see it,
otherwise you
can also check it by going to our website, it is
unheard of that on the same screen our result will be displayed.  The
question will be displayed to you,
visit it and give your answer and
exciting prizes GTA This whole
camp is about this death
rate, so many people leave their homes
but are unable to return, to make them safe,
we are engaged in this campaign to work on this fast, we are giving
our full contribution to change this thing
and we go, you also
contribute in it and become its lesson, by
bringing these small changes we will be able to
make our routes, we will be able to stop a syringe,
August sir, if we
understand our responsibilities and
follow our responsibilities, then somewhere or the other we will not be able to save our lives
without any problem, I will
request you to please be a part of them, we can bring
change on and
change everyday, if we all can understand that every
person can change himself, but if
we fulfill our responsibilities,
we will all follow our own rules,
sadly you will see that our roles will change to a
great extent, if  You must have seen
that in foreign countries there are a
lot of rules and regulations
and people follow a lot of rules
and somewhere you must have seen that you maintain a
safe distance while driving. You have to
follow all these rules for yourself,
not for others, not to show off to anyone else, not for
any policeman, not for
anyone else, it is for yourself,
that change and you should change it for yourself,
if you
drive with caution, you will not drink
and drive, you will not
use phone while driving, you will wear proper mirrors, you will
wear proper helmet, you will
not indulge in any such distraction, then
somewhere or the other we will only be
able to make our day, we will not have that accident because when we drive fast, then
you will
drive a car in a hurry, you will ride a bike or
two wheeler, if we
do things like that in the office, then the
chances of an accident become very less, so
we would request you to
follow all the things, please
never drive while driving because it  Not only
can you put your life in danger but also the lives of those who are going for Lokjagran around you
and this
intelligence is very risky, you will be risking yourself and along with that you will be
putting the lives of others and their families in danger as well, I
request you why don't you
please follow all the rules, any such
wall cream which question you have
into its time to participate in the
activities after two months the bank will come and come
with a new set of questions so you can be
part of dial 100 mystery question Albert
for you while driving UC August caring
vehicle and Guru sir product for drawing
art side you will speed up and worked with
sickle not registration number of then tomorrow
and inform authorities allowed to enter into pass
and [ __ ] I am a
lolly to shoulder splash so please be a
part of others and answer the answer this question on what has happened has happened which is why
you have pimples, the result of this is what
we are doing in Delhi  On this
our exam starts at 10:00 pm sorry ours comes
Ladli speaking, its results are out you
can also check by going to our website its result problem is
that we have daily missions and there also you will be
shown a part of 60 and you
can participate in this along with your
family and friends this is a chance to win
multiple gates you can participate in all
five questions on
e agree to all its business we have new
set of question for the 10,000 eleventh day
and a gruesome on telefilms of
representatives benefit and you can win some more
exciting prizes to have the question while
driving same if
sparing vehicle scientific proving that
side you will speed up and that does not
registration number of the white color and
authority apart that Bigg Boss and [ __ ] E M
Hawk Loot display that you have my screen par
jo yeh question hai you are going  You are
driving and then you see that the big
tricks that I will request for all the goods are
normal, the dip, the one
coming out of it is flying, so
what will you do during the exam, you will
increase your speed and overtake it and go ahead, you will
note down its registration number and
inform the authority or you will
let that Michael go and
after that you will go because it becomes very risky,
if such a voicemail is on your side, then on your
shoulder display, you will
inform by blowing the horn and yes but
traitor, then what will you do, please
tell your answer and the trees which are used are
very dangerous
because their balance is very
high, their dip v5, the
chances of their overturning are also very high, the chances of their Yagya
Chandsen accident are very
high, so now if you see this thing like this, then still now
maintain a distance and distance
with the Michaels because they become
very risky in growth and some
bhi main clear planning ho sakti hai
main to aane jaisi ki rekha today our
languages ​​have like 60 seconds question
of the day dream one questions left after
to earth one of michael jackson came in love continue to give a
set of questions so you
can benefit you have a chance to normal people give one answer questions
everyday we ram
with utility of every you have a chance to be a
part of the show will e dint of every day
a sanam
ki and rituals will be ahat results will be announced it's an
alarm it should
apply speaking in which way all want to
according result of the day should you can be tune with are also and you can see the
results on aa jaaye
pagla se maangna chahiye jis question while
driving same and goods caring
michael wagonr pro trading outside you
will speed up and what is the work has not
registration number of the white colour and
Inform authorities alarm difficult pass and
pushes loot display so you answer it
Chaddar Amrit thank you with Hindus should thank you so
much stay tuned soon stay
just close set up question of the world
time please like and stay with us ho
pawali spread to unlock Junaid thank you so much
for the day